[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the gestation period of the Giant Panda?", "correct_answer": "95-160 days", "incorrect_answers": ["40-50 days", "60-90 days", "90-120 days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Let me in!  Im so cold, pleads the ghost of Catherine Earnshaw. In what 1847 novel will you find the story of the doomed lovers Catherine Earnshaw and the wild gypsy Heathcliff?", "correct_answer": "Wuthering Heights", "incorrect_answers": ["Lorna Doone", "Jane Eyre", "Agnes Gray"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In India, they consider this body fluid a sedative, especially if it comes from an animal like the ox.   Some people who study yoga will use the human form of it.", "correct_answer": "Urine", "incorrect_answers": ["Sweat", "Saliva", "Blood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rabbits vomit often to get rid of whatever their stomach is unable to digest.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Grand Valley is an extended populated agricultural valley located along which US river?", "correct_answer": "Colorado River", "incorrect_answers": ["Alabama River", "Mississippi River", "Missouri River"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On The Rifleman series, Johnny Crawford\u2019s characters name was Matt.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who became famous in 1957 with the Jamaican folk song, The Banana Boat Song?", "correct_answer": "Harry Belafonte", "incorrect_answers": ["Charlie Parker", "Max Roach", "Miles Davis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is a normal post-prandial blood sugar?", "correct_answer": "Less than 140 mg/dl (7.8 mmol/L)", "incorrect_answers": ["Less than 125 mg/dl (6.9 mmol/L)", "Less than 160 mg/dl (8.9 mmol/L)", "Less than 200 mg/dl (11.1 mmol/L)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of a successful American musician, nicknamed The Jewish Elvis?", "correct_answer": "Neil Diamond", "incorrect_answers": ["Billy Diamond", "Rodger Diamond", "Walter Diamond"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During this year, Einstein had three incredible papers published in the physics journals, and obtained his doctoral degree.", "correct_answer": "1905", "incorrect_answers": ["1912", "1907", "1929"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Be careful how you use this name because Its off the record, on the QT and very hush-hush.\nIn what movie did the dying Det. Jack Vincennes whisper Rollo Tomasi helped solve the Nite Owl Murders?", "correct_answer": "LA Confidential", "incorrect_answers": ["LA Story", "The Untouchables", "The Usual Suspects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 300, the Spartans wore virtually no armor. Was this the way actual Spartans went into battle?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}]